nielit.gov.in 2019-08-18

# Privacy Policy | Government of India : National Institute of Electronics & Information Technology

## Error message

  * _User warning_ : The following module is missing from the file system: _webform_localization_. For information about how to fix this, see [the documentation page](https://www.drupal.org/node/2487215). in __drupal_trigger_error_with_delayed_logging()_ (line _1143_ of _/var/www/html/includes/bootstrap.inc_ ).
  * _Warning_ : Creating default object from empty value in _ctools_access_get_loggedin_context()_ (line _1411_ of _/var/www/html/sites/all/modules/ctools/includes/context.inc_ ).
  * _Warning_ : Creating default object from empty value in _ctools_access_get_loggedin_context()_ (line _1411_ of _/var/www/html/sites/all/modules/ctools/includes/context.inc_ ).

## You are here

HomePrivacy Policy

NIELIT - Website does not automatically capture any specific personal information from you, (like name, phone number or e-mail address), that allows us to identify you individually. If the NIELIT - Website requests you to provide personal information, you will be informed for the particular purposes for which the information is gathered and adequate security measures will be taken to protect your personal information.

We do not sell or share any personally identifiable information volunteered on the NIELIT - Website to any third party (public/private). Any information provided to this website will be protected from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

We gather certain information about the User, such as Internet protocol (IP) addresses, domain name, browser type, operating system, the date and time of the visit and the pages visited. We make no attempt to link these addresses with the identity of individuals visiting our site unless an attempt to damage the site has been detected.

Webmaster  
NIELIT - Website  
Fax: +91-11-24301851/862  
Email:   [webmaster@nielit.gov.in](mailto:webmaster@nielit.gov.in)

Language  English
